

Keagan Chisnall

Engineering Manager

Townsville, Australia

★ keagan@chisnall.io

% +61 412 891 641

Experiences

Software Engineering Manager (2021 - Now) SafetyCulture

Managed cross-functional teams of 5-12 engineers between Townsville, Sydney, and remote. Working with designers and product managers to deliver major user, group, and permission management features.

Startup Co-founder (2019 - 2020) *Medicly*

Co-founded a pharmaceutical information app for doctors to ensure affordability and availability of prescribed medication; with an MVP reached ~100 monthly doctors.

Management Consultant (2015 - 2019) Federal Government & Private

Diverse business support for small-medium sized businesses. This included remediating profitability or growth issues, workplace culture improvement plans, government grants, and general management coaching.

Area Manager (2012 - 2014)

Nalco Water, An Ecolab Company

Sales and engineering management of 8 staff across 4 remote locations. I was responsible for servicing, supporting, and growing a base of 150 customers, representing >\$4M annual sales.

Process Engineer (2008 - 2012)Sun Metals & Xstrata Technology

Broad process engineering and project management experience at various mineral processing locations. I primarily worked in R&D, specifically around leaching, electrolysis, and water treatment processes. This path culminated in consulting for a \$20M plant refurbishment project in the Philippines.

Summary

I've been a manager for 10 years and an engineer for 16. My experience spans from mining to pharmaceuticals, and from R&D to sales. I find passion and develop an interest in all I do; geeking out on technical excellence, and striving to know more than I did yesterday.

Skills

- Cross functional teams
- Hiring talent
- Sales
- Process improvement
- Product development
- Stakeholder management
- Strategic planning
- Quality control
- System design
- Delegation
- Team leadership
- Software development

Qualifications

Master of Management Monash University 2017 Second Class Honours, Division A

Bachelor of Engineering (Chem) James Cook University 2007 First Class Honours